<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HelloWorld</string>
    <string name="QuestionCSE">

        1.\n(a) Write the main feature of C language.\n\t\t
            (b) Define:\n\t\t\t
                    i)compiler.\n\t\t\t
                    ii)interpreter\n\t\t\t
                    iii)source code.\n
            (c) In the view of memory storage ,what is the difference between 25 and 25.07\n
            (d) Write a program to reverse a given number.\n\n
        2.\n(a) Differential between while and do while loop.	02\n
            (b) Determine the value of each of the  following logical expression if a=15,b=20 and c=-12	04\n
                \t\t\ti)	a==c||b>=a+5.\n
            (c) Write a program to check whether a given number  is the number of Fibonacci series or not.\n\n\n

	    3.\n(a) Assume that the following declaration have been made in the program	04\n
	            \t\tin year, count;\n
	            \t\tfloat amount, price;\n
                \t\tchar code, city[20];\n
	            \t\tdouble root;\n
            \t(b) When a switch statement is useful,explain briefly.	03\n
            \t(c) Explain the perpose of extern  and gets keywords.write a C program whice calculate the average value of	4 2/3\n\n\n

        4.\n(a) What do you mean by call by value and call by reference? Show the output of the following program.	04\n
	            \t\tint funct(int val,int *data){\n
		            \t\t\treturn((val++)+(*data)++);}\n
	            \t\tvoid main(){\n
		            \t\t\tint val*5,data*4;\n
		            \t\t\tprintf(“%d”,funct(data,**));\n
		            \t\t\tprintf(“%d%d”,val,data);\n
                \t\t}\n
        \t\t(b) Write a c program using recurslon which will calculate the value of nPr and nCr.	3 2/3\n
        \t\t(c) Distinguise between; 02\n
	        \t\t\ti)Local and Global variable.\n
	        \t\t\tii)Autometic and Static variable.\n
        	\t\t\t(a) Write a program to read a decimal number and print its octal equivalent number.	5 2/3\n\n\n

        5.\n(a) Write a program to print the following output using loop statement. Finally generate the program for ‘n’	06
           lines.
                  \t\t\t\t* * * * *
                  \t\t\t\t* * *  *
                    \t\t\t\t\t* * *
                     \t\t\t\t\t\t* *
                      \t\t\t\t\t\t\t*

            (b) Write a program to copy all the elements of a s*c array to be a 30 element one dimensional array.	5 2/3\n\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="QUESTIONeee">
        1.\n(a) Define the following:\n\t\t\t
                    i)Ideal and partial voltage and current sources.\n\t\t\t
                    ii)Active and passive elements.\n\t\t\t
            (b) State KVL and KCL.\n\n
        2.\n(a) What are the reasons for placing two or more batteries(voltage source) in parallel? Explain with circuit diagram.	02\n
            (b) Determine V and I for the following networks, if the resistance R2 is shorted out.	04\n
            (c) Determine the equivalent resistance of the following circuits.\n\n\n
        3.\n(a) ) Define the following:	04\n\t\t\t
                    i)	Active and passive elements.\n\t\t\t
                    ii)	Independent and dependent voltage source.\n

            (b) Write down the steps of determining Thevenin equivalent resistance involving circuit with only dependent source. Find the	6 2/3
value of source resistance RS so that maximum power delivered to the load is 20W.
\n\n
            4.\n(a) Determine the average power delivered to networks having the following input voltage and current.	6 2/3
	\n\t\t\t(i)   v=100 sin⁡(wt+40°)\n\t\t\t
    		  v=30 sin⁡(wt+70°)
	\n\t\t\t(ii)  v=140 sin⁡(wt-70°)\n\t\t\t
	      v=4 sin⁡(wt-50°)\n\n

        5.\n
        (a) Define power factor. Vectorically explain “capacitive networks have leading power factors and inductive networks have lagging	06
        power factor”.\n
        (b) Define phasor diagram.\n
    </string>

    <string name="QuestionMath">

        1.\n
        (a) Find from first principle the derivative of  x^x    (x>0)	04\n
        (b) Differentiate x^(〖sin〗^(-1) x ) with respect to 〖sin〗^(-1) x.\n\n

        2.\n
        (a) State and prove Roller’s theorem.	04\n
        (b) Define maximum and minimum of a function f(x) at x=a. Show that the minimum value of  x/logx is e\n
        (c) Evaluate: 〖lim┬(x→0)   〗⁡〖(〖(1+x)〗^(1/x)  -e)/x〗\n\n

        3.\n
        (a) find the condition that conics ax^2+by^2=1 and a_1 x^2+b_1 y^2=1 shall cut orthogonally.	04\n
        (b) If lx+my=1 touches the curve 〖(ax)〗^n+〖(by)〗^n=1 then show that	04\n
             \t\t〖(1/a)〗^(n/n-1)+〖(n/b)〗^(n/n-1)=1\n
        (c) Find the radius of curvature at the origin of the following curve: x^3+y^3=3axy\n\n

        4.\n
        (a) find the whole area of a cycloid x=a(θ+sinθ), y=a(1-cosθ), bounded by its base.	04\n
        (b) Find the volume and the surface area of the solid ngenerated by revolving the cardioide	04\n
           \t\tr=a(1-cosθ) about the initial line.

        \n(c) Find the volume intrinsic equation of the cardiodie	3 2/3\n\n
             \t\tr=a(1-cosθ), the arc being measured from the cusp(θ=0)\n\n

        5.\n
        (a) State and prove the Euler’s homogeneous function for three variables.	04\n
        (b) If x^2/a^2 +y^2/b^2 +z^2/c^2 =1 and x^2/(a^2+λ)+y^2/(b^2+λ)+z^2/(c^2+λ)=1 then prove that	3 2/3\n
            \t\t(x(b^2-c^2))/dx+(y(c^2-a^2))/dy+(z(a^2-b^2))/dz=0\n
        (c) Find the radius of curvature at any point for the curve x=a(θ-sinθ)  ,y=a(1-cosθ)\n\n

        6.\n
        	(a) Define Gamma and Beta function. Show that ¯( ) n+1) = n¯( ) n)	04\n
            (b) Obtain the reduction Function for ∫▒〖e^ax   〖cos〗^n   x  dx〗	04\n
            (c) Find the lengths of the loop of the curve x=t^2, y=t-1/3 t^3\n\n


    </string>
</resources>
